>> Brian Holt: 我们将进行代码分割。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
we're going to do code splitting.
接下来我需要重置我的存储库。
Next I need to reset my repo.
所以这就回到了一个我可以开始的状态
So that's back in a state where I can
start without emotion cuz that we wanna
从零开始就像我们忏悔的地方一样
start from ground zero like
a good place in our repo.
我要做的是我要来这里启动我的服务器
So what I'm gonna do is I'm gonna
come in here, start my server.
我会说 git
I'm gonna say git
重置 HEAD --硬的。
reset HEAD --hard.
现在，说这都是非常具有破坏性的操作。
Now, just saying this is all
very destructive operations.
所以，如果你想保留你的代码，不要这样做，对吗 ?
So, if you wanted to keep any of
your code, don't do this, right?
但我不想说让我重新考虑一下
But I don't so I'm just gonna say,
give me reset hard and so
现在你可以看到我创造的这两件事情会在这里
now you can see maybe the two
things that I created will be here.
再这样，除非你想破坏一切，否则不要这样做。
And so again, don't do this unless you
intend on like destroying everything.
你可以说 git clean -f。
You can say git clean -f.
这会清除在厨房里没有追踪的东西
That's going to clean everything
that's not tracked in git.
正如你想象的那样，这也许是你想留下的东西，但我不知道。
As you might imagine, that might be things
that you wanted to keep, but I don't.
>> Brian Holt: 我只是告诉你这是因为
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: I'm just telling
you this because one of
你会把你想要的东西删除你要怪我
you is gonna delete something that you
want it and you're gonna blame me and
我会说我告诉你的
I'm gonna say I told you so.
好吧那是以前从没发生过的
Okay, that's never happened before.
所以在这之后我会说我要在晚上再安装
So here after that, I'll do that I'm
gonna say npm install again just to get
一切都恢复了好状态
things back in a good state as well.
>> Brian Holt: 在每个分支之后，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
after every single branch,
每个模块都要这么做
you're gonna wanna have to do that or
after every module here.
这样你就能回到零状态了
So that you're back in kind
of a ground zero state.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，一切都好。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
everything should be good.
我们要继续进行代码分割
We're gonna move on to code splitting.
对于小型应用程序，代码分割是必不可少的，对吗 ?
Code splitting is essential for
small applications, right?
代码分割背后的理念是你不想
The idea behind code splitting
is that you don't wanna have to
把所有不重要的东西都装载在第一次装载的东西上对吧
load everything up front that's not
essential for the first page load, right?
所以如果我载入我网页的主页
So if I load a home page of my web page,
让我们来看这个， " 采用我 " 页面。
let's go look at this one,
the Adopt Me page.
那么让我们继续吧，在我们运行 npm 安装之后，让我们继续
So let's go ahead and after we run
the npm install, let's go ahead and
使我们的设备服务器运行。
get our dev server running.
因此，我将再次使用 npm 运行 dev 来启动服务器。
So I'm gonna say npm run dev
again to get our server started.
>> Brian Holt: 一旦装入，我们可以在 localhost 1234 处重新启动，好的。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Once that's loaded, we can
restart here at localhost 1234, okay.
>> Brian Holt: 现在这是正常状态。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
now this is back in a normal state.
所以我想说的是代码分割。
So what I wanna talk
about is code splitting.
代码分割允许您分割应用程序的部分
Code splitting allows you to split
out pieces of your application so
将装入延迟到更高版本。
that you defer the loading to later.
现在这很重要如果你想有个小的页面大小
Now this is essential if you
wanna have a small page size so
第一次装载的速度非常快
that the first load is really quick and
那么您可以将其他代码段的装入延迟到稍后，对。
then you can defer the loading of other
pieces of code until later, right.
所以举个例子，我在这个主页上，然后还有第二个
So for example, I'm on this homepage and
then I also have a second
页面称为 " 详细信息 " 页面，即此页面，对吗 ?
page here called the details page,
which is this page, right?
我不需要细节页面的所有代码直到后来，对吗 ?
I don't need all the code for
the details page until later, right?
因此，我可以将此代码的装入延迟到稍后，好吗 ?
So I can defer the loading of
this code until later, okay?
>> Brian Holt: 我可以做的是，我可以用几种不同的技术
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So what I can do here is I
can use a couple of different techniques
在 React 中延迟装入这些代码段。
within React to defer the loading
of these pieces of code later.
因此我可以拥有最小最快的初始页面负载，并且
So I can have the smallest,
fastest initial page load, and
那么我可以延迟加载新代码，直到稍后。
then I can defer loading
of new code until later.
>> Brian Holt: 因此，我希望您转至 app.js，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
I want you to go into app.js,
> > Brian Holt: 好的，然后在这里
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay and then up here we're
在这里进口两个新东西懒的
going to import two new things here, lazy,
L-A-Z-Y ，并带有大写字母 S 。
L-A-Z-Y and Suspense with a capital S.
>> Brian Holt: 好，现在我想推迟装货
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay,
now I wanna defer the loading
细节，对吧 ?
of Details until later, right?
只要包裹看到从这里进口的细节就像是
As soon as parcel sees import Details
from something here, it's like,
我要加载这个对吧
I need to load this, right?
这就包括在你的捆绑软件中
So it goes an includes
that in your bundle, but
我不想让它再这样了
I don't want it to do that anymore.
我要做的就是删除这个
So what I'm gonna do is
I'm gonna delete that.
>> Brian Holt: 在此应用上，我要说的是
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So above App here,
what I'm gonna say
我想说公寓细节懒惰
is I'm gonna say const Details = lazy,
具有 " 导入/ 详细信息 " 的功能。
with a function that says import./Details.
>> Brian Holt: 现在，什么是 " 详细信息 " ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now, what is Details?
那么详细信息现在是不会装入此代码的占位符组件
Well, Details is now a placeholder
component that will not load this code
直到后来细节才第一次被渲染
until later when Details is actually
tried to be rendered for the first time.
> > Brian Holt: 那么，我们还有一点事要做。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So,
we still have a little thing to do here.
所以在我们的上面
So, under our above router here,
我们会放一个悬念组件
we're gonna put a suspense component,
我们从雷法进口到路由器周围
which we import from React here,
around router.
> > Brian Holt: 然后我们会给它一个回退。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And
then we're gonna give it a fallback.
> > Brian Holt: 在这里，你只会给它一点标记，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: And here you're just
gonna give it a bit of mark up,
如果密码还没准备好就可以了
it's like show this if
the code is not ready yet.
所以我就会说 " 一号装载 " 路线
So I'm just gonna say h1 Loading route.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，现在我有了这个 " 详细信息 " 组件。
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
now I have this Details component.
这是一个懒惰加载的组件每当它运行时这个功能就在这里
This is a lazily loaded component,
this function here whenever it runs,
它将导入详细信息，称为动态导入。
it's going to import Details,
this is called dynamic import.
这不一定是 " 重要 " 的事。
This is not necessarily a React thing.
这是你说的一个 JavaScript 的东西
This is a JavaScript thing
that you're basically saying,
从某个地方动态导入这个东西对吧
dynamically import this from somewhere,
right?
然后派丝很聪明地说我知道该怎么做
And then Parcel is smart enough to say,
I know what to do with this, and
它会在此处分割代码并将其分割为单独的捆绑软件，对吗 ?
it does a code split here and
splits this into a separate bundle, right?
> > 布莱恩 - 霍尔特: 现在我们把这个悬念包裹在我们的路由器上
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Now we've wrapped this
suspense thing around our router
说，嘿，如果这里有东西要装载，
that says, hey,
if anything inside of here is loading,
不显示，首先显示此 h1 装入路径，直至此
don't show it, show this h1
loading route first until this
进口承诺会解决然后展示，对吧 ?
import promise resolves and
then show it, right?
> > Brian Holt: 那么现在，如果我在这里，我会硬刷新页面，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So now, if I go over
here and I'll hard refresh the page,
然后我们再看看 " 网络 " 标签
and we'll look at the Network tab.
>> Brian Holt: 在此处查看 JS ，请注意我已装入样式和应用，对吗 ?
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Look at the JS here, so
notice I've loaded style and App, right?
但如果我来这里寻找宠物
But if I come in here and
search for a pet and
我去找胖子 Slim 会把它装在下面
I go to Fat Boy Slim notice that it's
going to load a details.js down here.
>> Brian Holt: 好的，有 app.js 进来，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: Okay, so
there's app.js coming in, and
如果我点击这个 details.js 就可以了
if I click on this details.js
now is doing that.
我给你看是因为它挺快的
I show you that because it's pretty fast,
装的真难知道吗
it's really hard to
notice the loading right?
但是如果你在左上方很快发现，它会说加载，对吗 ?
But if you notice very quickly up here in
the top left it will say loading, right?
> > Brian Holt: 因此，我们分成 18 千字节，
&gt;&gt; Brian Holt: So
we split out 18 kilobytes,
18 千字节未压缩的 JavaScript。
which is 18 kilobytes of
uncompressed JavaScript.
这可能就像一个千字节的
This would end up being like one kilobyte,
probably.
所以这不值得，对吧 ?
So this is not worth it, right?
这会比现在慢一点
This is actually gonna be slower than,
你就应该把它包括在主丛里
you would've just rather have included
it in the main bundle to begin with.
所以如果你要做密码分割
So, if you are gonna do code splitting,
你应该至少把 30 千字节加出来
you should be splitting out
at least 30 kilobytes plus.